2gb-hosting.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy - 2GB Hosting

PRIVACY POLICY

This document outlines exactly what you are permitted and not permitted to do as a user of 2GB-Hosting. Note that by visiting 2GB-Hosting, you are an user of 2GB-Hosting and these rules apply to you. Using this site simply means visiting it, or downloading it.

**Your Privacy is Important**

2GB-Hosting respects the privacy and sensitivity of any information you may give us, and strives to protect this information for its intended uses. This document is meant to clearly outline how personal information given to us will be used.

**Information Collected and Uses**

2GB-Hosting chiefly collects personal information during the registration process. During this process, the following information are mandatory:

• Valid email address: The email address you provide us will only be used for account notifications, for example, when a video associated to your account is removed due to copyright concerns. It will also be used for statistics recovery and other affiliate services. Your email will not be disclosed to anyone

**2GB-Hosting also runs 3rd-party advertisements and statistics software.**

The information collected by these programs may include your IP address and various other non-personal information such as the city of your Internet Service Provider. In addition, your response to certain advertisements (e.g. by clicking on them) may cause the advertiser to profile you in a certain demographic, so as to provide ads more relevant to your needs. Rest assured that no personally-identifying information will be given to third-party ad servers. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

If you decide to to contact us, your email and name will remain confidential and be used solely for communicating with you regarding the subject of the contact.

Finally, any marked "public" videos published by you are published with the clear intention for them to be publicly viewable.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your information will NOT be used for any purposes other than those outlined above. Information will not be sold or given willingly to a third party for any non-related purposes. Our web servers are securely hosted to prevent unauthorized access.

In short, your information is safe at 2GB-Hosting

Our Policy on Content Removal

Please note that 2GB-Hosting reserves the right to remove any video uploaded by any user without issuing any kinds of notices. 2GB-Hosting respects the rights of content distributors and replies promptly to any requests for the removal of copyrighted content

If you have found an infringing video, please contact us directly using the our Contact Form.
